So hello guys namaskar good evening to all of you
in our video and today friends we have
come to give some information in this video with the help of which you will get a
benefit friends you can also get double benefit from
above friends you are
also getting a chance to earn extra income okay
so friends if a new feature is added in the tell me then there are
no new features friends friends it is already there so a
lot of brothers have
commented on us that brother how do we have to do the registration process of
our PO SP of a payments bank,
how will I get it or not, a
lot of brothers are commenting about it
so friends let me
tell you the complete details about it in this video today
what does POS P mean,
what is POS P and what facilities will you get in POS P agent,
okay so
finally I will tell you the complete details about it
and you will have to watch our video from A to JD in
which friends
you will get support and
you will also get help in these features okay so let me
try to show you
this video of ours  You guys keep watching inside
and I am going to show you, so
friends, you will not get this update on the desktop,
where will you get this update, friends, you will get it
in Mi Pop, okay here, friends,
the update is going to be available in Mi Pop,
so I will try you guys, you will
mostly find it by logging in to the Mi Pop application,
if you are
searching for where is POP by opening the desktop, then you will
not find it, right, so you guys do not
ignore this video because
I will tell you completely about POS P agent
registration, what are the features, what facilities will you get,
what will you get in POS P,
friends, I will
tell you from A to Z, so guys, what will you get in POS P,
okay, a lot of
people's question is
what facilities will we get in POS P registration
and what documents do we
need, then we can register for POS P,
so friends, if I finally
tell you, then friends, I had done the registration
but after doing a little half,
friends, I left it, that is, if I say, then
here is the time and condition  It is more, so that's why
I took one process and
left this process, so what can we do here,
in PO SP, the PO
SP which will be called post and agent registration,
if we will get it
here, then you
can see it here, friends, I had
also done registration here, which you can see,
friends, some of my details have been completed
and some of
my details have not been completed yet, okay, friends, when
we click on complete, then
here it asks us for education
certificates etc., so
friends, maximum friends, here
you will need 10th pass marksheet, the
marksheet of 10th pass, friends, you will have to
upload it there on the front and back
side and from above, friends, and also like I
will click on PO P here, then there is
an exam here, friends,
we will have to give that exam, when friends, we
qualify in the exam, then
friends, our agent ID of POP,
friends, our open will open there,
friends, this is the update, friends,
I am showing you  Let me tell you friends, we do a
lot of trading of account opening, recharge, BVPS, like
after watching the video, there is a maximum 5 minute video, 3
minute video and after we watch that video, we
automatically have to
wait for a maximum of 5 minutes,
after that it opens for answers,
but it is the same here also,
friends, when you upload the complete document, then the
exam mark sheet will be uploaded and the
IIB which is being told to you here, like the live
exam will be here, the live exam will be general
exam here and personal details are also being
shown here and the training will also be
taken from you, the training of which will be there and IIB will have to be
uploaded here. IIB friends,
when we click on IIB here, then
friends, you will
not need to enter IIB, but you will have to
enter the mark sheet,
when we click on complete here, then
some videos for insurance
etc. will come here, we will have to watch the video in that also,
when friends, we will watch the
trending video,
then friends, our work is  Yes
friends, we will be able to do general insurance work,
so this is
for insurance friends and if those
people friends do not want to register for PO SP, then there is no such
problem here, there is no such
rule that you have to register for PO SP
otherwise
you will not get any service in these futures, there is nothing like that
friends, if you people
want to do POP REST then you
can do it, if you people do not want to do it then there is
no tension, friends,
maximum friends, you will take training of 15 hours here
and friends, you will have to appear for the
exam here and
if I share some information with you friends, then
here friends,
if I
tell you friends, there cannot be any such
special thing here for us, who is
giving us the process here, then it will
not be that good here, maybe we will see
what is happening or not happening,
we will see in these futures
and right now, for us, if we say
friends,
if we talk to the current system, then our work etc. is
not getting done here, so let's watch this video
You people have got this information inside it,
if you like this video then
like it and first of all subscribe to the channel,
in future you will keep getting
more such videos from us,
so thank you.